<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hello on Blogging like a billionare</title>
    <link>https://matthew.nz/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hello on Blogging like a billionare</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-nz</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:53:36 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://matthew.nz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Reflections on Retros</title>
      <link>https://matthew.nz/retros/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:53:36 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew.nz/retros/</guid>
      <description>I have a beef with Scrum Retrospectives when we create actions without owners, avoid difficult conversations, and don&amp;rsquo;t see changes over time. The format does not get outcomes for me, but it seems true for those operating at Senior levels or above.&#xA;I prefer to take proactive steps adjust the team environment. I do this by taking action and directly talking to stakeholders. That could mean include engaging delivery managers, creating Architectural Decision Records to align on a technical implementation, or promoting best practice through pairing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Landscaping: Methods for adapting code safely</title>
      <link>https://matthew.nz/refactoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 08:24:01 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://matthew.nz/refactoring/</guid>
      <description>Working titles:&#xA;Landscaping Tricks: Safety adapting code to develop insight Outline&#xA;Pitch: Most of our time is spent understanding code, so &amp;ldquo;readability&amp;rdquo; is the only way to speed up Code Smells Introduction: The best way to make progress is by recognising when something can be better (Cultivating Instinct) Catalogue Introduction Top 5: What refactoring patterns get you the greatest return for the least input Reviewers - Using stacked Pull Requests is kinder for reviewers Tests - How to reshape your architecture in the presence of tight mocking Conclusion: Code Fearlessly DJ Feedback:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
